hollister.com 2016-11-20

# Privacy Policy, Safe Harbor, Cookie Usage | Hollister US

## Privacy Policy

#### Privacy Policy

This section states the Privacy Policy under which you, the website visitor ("You”, “Your”, or “Yourself") may use or correspond with this website (the “Website”), which is owned by Hollister Incorporated ("We", "Us", "Our", or “Hollister”).

We respect Your privacy and want to protect Your personal information for the purpose of serving You better. The principles outlined in this Privacy Policy describe Our practices regarding the collection, use, and disclosure of information, including personally identifiable information (“PII"). PII is information that can be used to uniquely identify, contact, or locate a single person or can be used with other sources to uniquely identify a single individual. PII can be in any media or format, including computerized or electronic records, as well as paper-based files, for example: name, email, and mailing address, that You may provide.

**Please read this Privacy Policy before using this Website or submitting personal information to us. If You do not accept this Privacy Policy, please do not use this Website.**

#### Voluntary Submission of Information

You may use this Website without disclosing personally identifiable information, and We will not obtain such information about You unless You choose to submit it.

Any information You submit directly to Hollister will be used as provided in this Privacy Policy. If You send Us information via email or otherwise, You agree that We may contact You using various methods, such as postal mail, phone, or email. For security reasons, We do not recommend that You provide or share sensitive personal information — such as passwords, social security numbers, or bank account information.

#### Use of Collected Information

The information that Hollister collects is to better serve You, the customer. The information collected may include, but is not limited to, name, postal address, telephone number, email address, and products used. The information is collected, for example, through this Website, mail, email, and over the phone. We collect, maintain, and use the information You give Us to fulfill Your orders and sample requests, respond to Your inquiries, send You promotional offers and product information, deliver product support, and improve Our products and services. Hollister will not sell or rent Your personal information without Your consent. Where possible, We will explain the reasons why Your information is being collected and where You may exercise options to limit the collection of that information.

#### Cookies

This section states information on cookies under which you, the Website visitor (”You”, “Your”, or “Yourself”) may use or correspond with this Website (the “Website”), which is owned by Hollister Incorporated (”We”, "Us", “Our”, or “Hollister”).

A cookie is a simple text file that is stored on Your computer hard-drive or mobile device by a website’s server, and only that server will be able to track certain information. Each cookie is unique to Your web browser, enabling Us to track and target Your interests and enhance improvements on Our Website. For example, cookies usually allow Your browser to remember which sections You have visited and help Us to know how much traffic Our Website receives.

Cookies improve things by:

  * Remembering settings, so You don’t have to keep re-entering them whenever You visit a new page
  * Remembering information You have provided (e.g., Your postcode) so You don’t need to keep entering it
  * Measuring how You use the Website so We can make sure it meets Your needs

Our cookies are not used to gather any of Your personally identifiable information, but rather used to make this Website work better for You. Indeed, You can manage and/or delete these small files as You wish.

#### Managing Cookies

Some cookies are strictly necessary in order to enable You to move around this Website and use its features. Without these cookies, We will not be able to determine the number of unique users of this Website or provide certain features, such as automatic sign-in to Our services.

If You find cookies objectionable, it is possible to block some or all cookies, or even to delete cookies that have already been set. You can do this through Your browser settings, and the Help function within Your browser may have instructions on how to do this. Alternatively, You may wish to visit [www.aboutcookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/ "Managing Cookies"), which contains comprehensive information on how to do this with a wide variety of web browsers.
